themoneyconverter.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy and Cookie Usage

## Visitors To Our Website

This website is for information purposes only and does not require you to register as a user or to enter any personal information. 

However, when someone visits themoneyconverter.com we use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information, on its own, does not allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. 

We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. 

This website is funded by displaying advertisements and the details of our key advertising partners are given below. 

## Use Of Cookies 

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. 

Your cookie choices can be changed at any time by clicking on the icon in the bottom left corner of the page. 

### Universal Analytics (Google Analytics)

These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. 

The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. Google Analytics stores IP address anonymously on its servers in the US, and neither themoneyconverter.com or Google associate your IP address with any personally identifiable information. 

These cookies are set only after the user has given consent to us to use cookies and can be revoked by the user at any time. 

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, visit [Opt-Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

### Advertising (Google Adsense)

This website relies on advertising revenue to keep our services free for all users. All these ads are served via the Google Adsense program and use cookies to provide the ad experience. The data that they collect will also be subject to their own privacy policies and they may allow other companies to use cookies and tracking technologies to collect information about your website usage and your interaction with their adverts. To find out more click [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). 

#### Personalized Ads

Our advertising partners may collect and analyse data about you and your device from across other online services. This data helps to predict what might interest you and show you adverts tailored to those interests. 

#### Non-Personalized Ads

Non-personalized ads are ads that are not based on a user’s past behaviour. They are targeted using contextual information, including coarse (such as city-level) geo-targeting based on current location, and content on the current site or current query terms. Although these ads don’t use cookies for ad personalization, they do use cookies to allow for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting, and to combat fraud and abuse. 

## User anonymity and personal information

Log files are maintained of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the IP address of the user, which is automatically recognised by our web servers. Analysis of these log files is used to monitor website usage. These analyses may be made available to themoneyconverter.com staff and partner agencies to allow them to measure, for example, overall popularity of the site and typical user paths through the site. 

We will make no attempt to track or identify individual users, except where there is a reasonable suspicion that unauthorised access to systems is being attempted. In the case of all users, themoneyconverter.com reserves the right to attempt to identify and track any individual who is reasonably suspected of trying to gain unauthorised access to computer systems or resources operating as part of themoneyconverter.com web services. 

You should be aware, however, that access to web pages will generally create log entries in the systems of your ISP or network service provider. These entities may be able to identify the client computer equipment used to access a page. Such monitoring would be done by the provider of network services and is beyond the responsibility or control of themoneyconverter.com. 

As a condition of use of this site, all users must give permission for themoneyconverter.com to use its access logs to attempt to track users who are reasonably suspected of gaining, or attempting to gain, unauthorised access. All log file information collected by themoneyconverter.com is kept secure and no access to raw log files is given to any third party. 

## How do I change my cookie settings?

Your cookie choices can be changed at any time by clicking on the icon in the bottom left corner of the page. 

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).
